<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on fawx</title>
    <link>https://fawx.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on fawx</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 15:07:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fawx.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi, Kiddo.</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2015-03-19-hi-kiddo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2015-03-19-hi-kiddo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure when you&amp;rsquo;ll receive this.  Time machines, even the ones that only travel forward, are tricky to aim.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Ode to Set Intersection</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2009-10-26-an-ode-to-set-intersection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2009-10-26-an-ode-to-set-intersection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This here is Norman Casagrande, last.fm’s former head researcher and my former mentor.  The facial expression seen here is one of my favorites.  It’s usually accompanied by some questionably-translated Italian aphorism, ”You know, Erik, that is like the ox saying ‘horned’ to the donkey.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiev</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2006-01-31-kiev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2006 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2006-01-31-kiev/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Haven&amp;rsquo;t you ever wondered why the Church doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow women to be preachers?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Not specifically,&amp;rdquo; I replied, throwing my pack on the bed. I sat down. Icelandic Pizza Chef sat down on the opposite bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It makes God less attractive to women, so they all become whores and drug addicts.&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulaan Baatar</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-29-ulaan-baatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-29-ulaan-baatar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Mom!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember when I called you from the post office in Ulaan Baatar? The conversation was short, and I probably sounded distracted. Here’s why:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naushki</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-28-naushki/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-28-naushki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s easier to handle the vastness of the Gobi desert if one approaches it through Siberia. The brainstuff is already properly tenderized, prepared to handle the gradient of bleak to bleaker.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khuzhir</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-23-khuzhir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-10-23-khuzhir/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Khuzhir is the only town on Olkhon, which is the only island on Lake Baikal, which is the only lake in the world that has no lakes older than it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodstock</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-20-woodstock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-20-woodstock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I took an unofficial break from my official tour in Woodstock, New York. Little did I know that I had picked the one place in the country that seemed wholly crafted, from its geology to its local culture, to be the perfect retreat. Janie took me in for a few days and gave me the best overview of Woodstock I could ever hope for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-15-newyork/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-15-newyork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been here for a fortieth of a millennium, and I still haven&amp;rsquo;t learned the formula governing my admiration for another person. Sometimes I recognize a certain grace, a magnanimous spirit, or perhaps simply an overwhelming congeniality. It&amp;rsquo;s the kind of quality that makes me lean back in my seat and say, &amp;ldquo;Now so-and-so, boy, what a character!&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington, D.C.</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-07-washington-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-07-washington-dc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If every city of the world was a flavor of icecream, I would describe Washington, DC as Neopolitan. It’s rather unextraordinary yet dependable, plain but accomodating, and if you have discerning taste, you chomp the hell out of that chocolate section, and leave the strawberry and vanilla for someone else. Leah and Carrie helped me do just that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Road</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-06-on-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-06-06-on-the-road/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I continued my Kindness of Strangers tour, from Jacksonville up to Washington, DC. I posed the world a question, and it issued forth a resounding reply.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Havana Exit</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-25-havana-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-25-havana-exit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Down to my last few pesos, I spent my final two days in Cuba relaxing, recovering, and taking it all in one last time. I knew I wasn’t likely to return for years, and that when I did return, Cuba would be a very different place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinidad</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-23-trinidad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-23-trinidad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the next few days in Trinidad, an old Spanish colonial town that was gussied up in the early 19th century when French planters arrived, having fled from a particularly unpleasant slave revolution in Haiti.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viñales</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-18-vinales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-18-vinales/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Escaping Havana, I spent the next three days in Viñales and the surrounding countryside. Full of new people and new scenery, my days became somehow more relaxing and more hectic at the same time – perhaps I was beginning to follow the rhythm I could feel in the land and its people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Havana</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-17-havana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2005 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2005-04-17-havana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do not debauch. I certainly never cavort, save for the occasional quiet, metered cavort. So it was with some measure of surprise that I found myself swept away into Havana&amp;rsquo;s nightlife.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Temptation</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2004-06-06-last-temptation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2004 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2004-06-06-last-temptation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i can only attribute so much of last week and this weekend to divine providence. and i can really only focus on certain parts. but that’s how memory works – looping over itself in the space behind your eyes, allowing light through sort of distorted, kaleidoscopic, folding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Genitalia</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2004-04-25-primary-genitalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2004 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2004-04-25-primary-genitalia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;to take advantage of one of the last free weekends i&amp;rsquo;m going to have for a while, eric and i carted our way out to the mountains. eric found an old map of the logging roads in the jemez wilderness, and noticed that one of them came within a quarter mile of the san antonio hot springs, which was especially nice because the main trail to the hot springs is closed for another month or so, till the last of the snow melts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Mystery Tour</title>
      <link>https://fawx.com/post/2001-12-25-magical-mystery-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2001 15:07:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fawx.com/post/2001-12-25-magical-mystery-tour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i bought naola a plane ticket back to miami for christmas, but being short for cash, i bought myself a bus ticket. i’m no stranger to greyhound and i’ve come to expect the kind of weird shit that always happens to me on these buses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>